http://virtualtrials.com/privacy.cfm

Brain Tumor News
Fundraising For Research!
Gliadel® Wafer
Optune™ (Novocure NovoTTF-100A®)
Virtual Trial
What Is It?
Join
Post An Update
Map of Participants
Interact
Webinars Discussion Forum (NEW!)
Special Research Funds
Immunotherapy Research FundOligo FundOncoSynergy GBM Trial FundRosenbaum GBM Research Fund
Memorial and In Honor Donations
A-E
Bender, Sharon Bode, Bruce Bundick, John A. Cannon, Paula Card, Andy Chakravorty, Satya
Coney, Mark Cooper, Francis Xavier Davis, Susan Dickens, Brian
Eichinger, Shawn Erickson, Priscilla J.
F-M
Fels, Frederic Edward Finn, Vivienne Cecilia Freeland, Donald G. Friesenhahn, Cynthia Gayle
Gomory, Stephen Henry Hansen, Muriel Elyned Hicks, Don Roger Kralik, Patricia Lisciandra, Filippa Martin, Paul McGoff, Matthew Grady Molloy, James Mosic, Ronald Moss, Robert Musella, Ken
N-R
Nelson, Mark Thomas Neveaux, Mary O'Brien, Shannon Panker, Sandra Sue Parks, Laura Marie Peters, Meredith Dale Ride The Divide Robinson, Laurie Jean
Rogat, Aaron Douglas Rose, Catherine
Roth, Rona
S-Z
Salkowski, Mark S. Sfeir, Nadine Stanziale, Marie Stott, Michael
Timmons, Steven L. Walker, Ruth Wetzel, Christi
Zeilstra, Steve Zimmerman, Gayle H
Policies
Last Updated: 5/27/18
PRIVACY POLICY Version: 4 (adopted 5/27/18)
The Musella Foundation For Brain Tumor Research & Information, Inc is committed to responsible information handling practices. You can visit most pages on our websites (as defined below) without giving us any information about yourself, but sometimes we need your information to provide services that you request. This Privacy Policy explains data collection and use in those situations. By visiting our websites, you consent to the information practices described in this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy applies to the following sites (as well as subdomains of these websites):
Virtualtrials.com
Virtualtrials.org
WalkToEndBrainTumors.org
BrainTumorCopays.org
We have no control over the websites we link to, so this Privacy Policy does not apply when you follow a link off of one of our websites.
This policy is subject to change. The first time you visit the website after the policy changes, you will be asked to agree to the policy.
What type of information does we collect and how is the information used?
For Donors to our organization:
We collect your name, contact information and possibly your relationship to brain tumors. We do not collect your credit card information. This information is used internally and is never shared or sold to any other person or organizations. We may send you a mailing at least once a year telling you of our accomplishments and requesting another donation. You can easily opt out by telling us to remove your name from our mailing list.
For participants in the Virtual Trial project:
We collect your details medical information including: Your and your contact person's name and contact information, your doctor's name and contact information, as well as your diagnosis, treatment history and medical reports. We are in a collaboration with xCures and Cancer Commons to help analyze the data. We will share your information with them. None of these organizations will sell or share your personal data.
For visitors to our website:
If you voluntarily fill out a form, we will collect the information from that form. That information will be used for the intended purposes of the form and will not be shared or sold to any other person or organization. For example, if you order a "Guide For The Newly Diagnosed", we will use your contact information to mail you a copy of the guide â€“ but you will not be put on a mailing list to solicit donations.
Infomation we collect automatically without you expressly giving it to us:
Certain information will be collected from all visitors to any of our websites listed above:
Your web browser will automatically send and we may retain information such as:
Your IP address and location
Type of software you are using
Which site you were on directly before going to our website
Your domain name
Cookies:
We use cookies to customize your user experience and to allow us to tell if you already agreed to the privacy policy or not.
Google Analytics
We use a tool called "Google Analytics" to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use (as amended for government websites) and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.
The reports we get do NOT show your name or provide any way that we could tell who you are. They just show us aggregate information such as how our visitors got to our website, what browser they use, general location, and the language used. There is no way to opt out of this tracking.
Credit Card Policy:
When you use a credit card on any of our websites (see list of websites above), we use a secure connection to the PayPal Credit Card Processor to complete the transaction immediately. At no time do we save your credit card number, expiration date or security code. No employees or volunteers of our organization can even see your credit card information. Paypal will have access to your name, contact information and credit card information. Check their privacy policy to see how they may use it: https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full Do not make a credit card donation or purchase on our website if you do not accept PayPal's privacy policy!
How Long We Keep This Information
We may keep information we collect forever. You may request that we delete all identifiable information that we have on you at any time.
Law Enforcement
IF we are compelled to divulge your information by law enforcement, we will
Advertising Policy
All of our services are free to you, including: our extensive video library, our "Guide for the newly diagnosed brain tumor patient", online support groups, extensive library of original articles, brain tumor news blast, toll free patient help line, co-payment assistance program, drug discount card program and much more.
These programs cost a lot of money to provide to you. We (the executive board of the Musella Foundation For Brain Tumor Research & Information, Inc) have decided to accept sponsorships and advertising on our website and newsletters to offset these costs, instead of charging you for this potentially life saving information. Our thoughts are that our efforts can help the most people if it is free to them, so we accept advertising and sponsorship.
Most - or all - of income from sponsorship and advertising comes from the companies that make products needed by the brain tumor community. Sponsorship is in the form of unrestricted educational grants. These companies are acknowledged on our sponsors page. There are policies in place to prevent any influence of the sponsors on the editorial content of this website. Our editor is a paid employee of the Musella Foundation For Brain Tumor Research & Information, Inc, but his salary is in no way influenced by any of the sponsors. The salary is not based on how many sponsors participate, how much they give or if we lose a sponsor. His salary is set by the executive committee without any input from the sponsors.
We reserve the right to reject any advertising that is against our mission and will not accept any advertising that we feel is not in the best interest of brain tumor patients. The appearance of an advertisement on virtualtrials.com (or in our newsletters or support groups) is not an endorsement of the sponsor. We are not responsible for the content of the ads. We suggest that you look at the ads and if the product or service looks good to you, bring it to your doctors and discuss it with them.. Our main purpose is to give you the information you need to find and understand the options - not to make the decisions for you.
All advertising on the site is will be clearly identified as advertising and is kept separate from editorial content - always enclosed in a box that says SPONONSORED BY or SPONSORED LINKS.
The sponsors do not sponsor a particular page - the order of the banners is random. Every time you reload a page, the banner ad changes to the next sponsor in the rotation. The only exception to this rule is the trial listings - where we allow sponsors to select the category to sponsor such as trials for a particular tumor type, treatment type or geographical area. Those ads are clearly marked as SPONSORED LINKS and are always for a trial for the selected category.
Editorial Policy
We make every effort to provide you with balanced, responsible, encouraging, and thorough information. All content has been reviewed by health care professionals. In some cases, articles are written by patient advocates - these articles are always reviewed by a health care professional before being posted on our website. The only exception to this rule is the survivor stories - which are written by the brain tumor patient or caregiver. We feel that it is not appropriate to change their words.
We maintain complete editorial independence and separation from advertisers and sponsors at the site. None of the content is screened, altered, or edited by sponsors at any time.
Returns Policy
If you make a donation online and change your mind within 24 hours, use our feedback form and tell us to cancel the donation. After 24 hours, call us at 888-295-4740 and we can cancel the donation only if the tax receipt and/or acknowledgement to the family hasn't been mailed out yet.
If you make a donation by mail and want to change your mind, call us at 888-295-4740 and we can cancel it only if the tax receipt and/or acknowledgement to the family hasn't been mailed out yet.
If you buy a ticket to one of our events, you can cancel and get a refund up to 48 hours before the event. Call us at 888-295-4740 to cancel. If you received an actual ticket in the mail, you must return the ticket at least 48 hours before the event so we can resell it.
Bad Check Policy
There is a $25 charge for bounced checks plus the amount of the check.
Shipping Policy
If you purchases something from us, we will ship it within 1 week, with the exception of tickets which we usually (check event page for details) ship a few days before the event. If you need something in a hurry - call us before ordering and we can tell you if it is possible to ship it immediately!
Home |
Brain Tumor Guide |
FAQs |
Find A Treatment
Noteworthy Treatments
|
News |
Virtual Trial |
Copyright (c) 1993 - 2020 by: The Musella Foundation For Brain Tumor Research & Information, Inc1100 Peninsula BlvdHewlett, NY 11557888-295-4740
